sup everyone T5 here with a very special
video today now I thought today to do
something a little bit more special and
[__] I thought instead uploading like a
normal like SOC episode I thought today
I would tell like a little story time
time out what the [__] who the [__] help
help someone tried to mug me get off me
who are you get get off my ass I'll beat
your ass come on [__] come on what the
wait are you wearing a modern song sh is
that my sock [__] you're willing [__]
I'll beat your [__] ass get over here
get why you running I'll beat your
[__] ass he yeah you how you like
that [__] come on come on I'll beat
your [__] ass you trying to attack
your sock off F get come on trying you
mug me you mug me 25 [__] I'll be your
[__] ass come on come on fight me
fight me [__] come on
come on come on come on I've been
waiting for this I've been waiting for
this help help he's got M me he was
anyways you guys seen this
[__] get back up get back up I said get
back up if you if you don't get back up
I'm not going to let you go you know
what wait right
there you know what Daddy needs to take
a [__] [__] anyways open your mouth
open it right now I'm going to give I'm
going to give you your Just Desserts
[__] yeah you like that here it comes
again that that's what I thought I hope
you like that I had better not see you
around here again
[__]
I love St onr